NYILINKINDI MUNEZERO Jean Jacques

jacknyilinkindi@gmail.com - (+250) 787 914 693 KG 61 St, Kigali Rwanda

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a young man interested in computer related fields like programing, networking, system analysing and data security. This document contains most of my achievements, projects that I worked on and goals I would like to attain.

I would like to see the world change through turning my bright ideas into global solutions in order to transform lives and develop personally.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Time Senior Developer - March 2016 - Now

SpiderBit – <u>www.spiderbit.rw</u> KG 68 St & Telecomm House, Kigali

Responsibilities:

- Web Designer
- Web App Developer
- System Analyst
- SMS Application Developer

Part Time Web Designer - December 2015 - Now

Technology Agents Rwanda Centenary House, Kigali

Responsibilities:

- Web Designer
- Analyst

Part Time Senior Developer - December 2015 - Now

Native Box Rwanda - www.nativeboxrw.com KCT, Kigali

Responsibilities:

- Web Designer
- Web App Developer
- System Analyst
- Mobile App Developer

Internee - December 2014 - January 2015

Prime Life Insurance Company- www.prime.rw KN 3 St, Kigali, RSSB Building

Responsibilities:

- Working' on Prime Asset Management Software
- IT Help Center

LANGUAGES SPOKEN

- KINYARWANDA
- ENGLISH
- FRENCH
- SWAHILI

EDUCATION

Advanced-Level, 2013 - 2015

SOS Technical High School, Kigali, Rwanda

Ordinary-Levels, 2011 - 2012

Kiserian Junior Seminary, Kajiado North, Kenya

Primary Schools(P2-P6), 2006 - 2010

La Fontaine Primary School, Kigali, Rwanda

Nursery + Primary Schools(N1-P1), 2001 - 2005

APACOPE School,

Kigali, Rwanda

PROJECTS WORKED ON

RwandaGuide

A mobile app that helps users to know places in Rwanda and their contacts.it also guides the user where he/she would like to go. The amazing part of it is that it works offline that makes it different from other guiding apps that use Google map thus requires internet connection. I worked on it under HeHE Ltd Mentorship.

NY LAN Chat

A software that helps it's users to exchanged text messages over a local network. The amazing part of the software is that it doesn't require internet connection even when internet connection is off you can still exchange messages. It can be used in companies, hospitals or any other institutions. I worked on it personally as my End High School Project.

Smart School Card

With the name you can guess what it is. It is a system that generates student cards equipped with a QR .When any person scans the QR Code using a Smart Phone or other devices is able to know whether the card is valid and is even able to directly call parents/guardian of the student if needed. I worked on it personally.

DUKA

A web application that is used in small and large businesses for the management of the sales, purchases, store and other business transaction for keeping track of the business development and how your products are bought and many other amazing features.DUKA has different versions depending on business models those are distribution,reseller,industry,etc. I worked on it under SpiderBit Ltd. Link: duka.rw

• Clinic Plus

A application that manages clinic activities, patients information, statistical data and reporting system for the clinic to keep track of how many patients were affected by specific disease and many more functions for making work easier.

I worked on it under SpiderBit Ltd.

Alumni Connect

A web platform that is used by SOS Technical High School Alumni (Am part of the group). This platform allows alumni to stay in touch and this platform helps the school in statistics and data collection where by the school knows what each alumnus is doing outside whether he/she has a job or not and how many alumni created their own companies. Alumni benefit in the platform usage because the school post available job offers for them to apply. Link: alumniconnect.soshgths.org I worked on it personally.

DOXA

A web application that is used in large businesses for the management of the sales, purchases, store and other business transaction for keeping track of the business development and how your products are bought.DOXA is mainly made in three categories which are Human Resource,Logistics and Accounting.The three make it possible to keep track of the whole organisation and also helps in taking managerial decisions depending the results provided. I worked on it under SpiderBit Ltd.

• eHAHO

A web platform that is used by farmers, Agrodealers, buyers and resellers, farmer promoters and partners (eg NGOs) and other users in agriculutural daily activitities. eHAHO helps farmers request for seeds and other inputs quickly and the hereby concerned approves the requests. It also helps everyone interested in knowing the market price all over the country or on a specific market and product easily by sending an SMS or visiting the platform. EHaho is used by NGOs that help farmers in communicating with them easily and faster. We are still working on new amazing features for making it a great product. Link: ehaho.rw I worked on it under SpiderBit Ltd.

CERTIFICATES

- Mobile App Development(HeHe Ltd) July 2015
- DIPLOME D'ETUDES EN LANGUE FRANÇAISE DELF B2 July 2016
- Entrepreneurship Training Certificate (Digital Opportunity Trust Rwanda) April 2017

CHARACTER

- Adventurous: I take risks.
- Ambitious: I am driven to succeed.
- Approachable: I work well with others.
- Calm: I stay level headed in a crisis.
- Competitive: I thrive under pressure.
- Confident: I am not afraid to ask questions.
- Cooperative: I get along well in a team setting.
- **Creative**: I think outside the box.
- Honest: I value integrity.
- Organized: I am a meticulous planner.
- Patient: I am not easily ruffled.
- Punctual: I have great time management skills.
- Technological: I am industrially savvy.

PERSONAL INTERESTS

- Coding
- Playing Video Games
- Recycling Items
- Saving
- Studying systems structure
- Helping Others
- Research
- Travelling

REFERENCES

- CEO SpiderBit (+250) 788647117 / mdavo12@gmail.com
- CEO Technology Agents Ltd (+250) 788303024
- CEO Native Box Rwanda (+250) 788737814

I, NYILINKINDI MUNEZERO Jean Jacques declare that everything written in this document is true and genuine.